<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ross Lazerowitz</title>
    <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ross Lazerowitz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosslazer.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GPT4: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love LLMs</title>
      <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/gpt4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosslazer.com/posts/gpt4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://rosslazer.com/images/gpt4-blog-header.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Header&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been internally conflicted about the rapid developments of Large Language Models (LLMs), like GPT4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HN Denizen Jason Hansel left a comment on &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35203262&#34;&gt;Tim Bray&amp;rsquo;s The LLM Problem&lt;/a&gt; that is the best summary of how I feel:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I agree with the general point that there is, at present, far too much uncertainty to understand the long-term effects of LLMs. It will be somewhere on the scale between &amp;ldquo;semi-useful toy,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;ends white-collar work as we know it,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;accidentally destroys mankind.&amp;rdquo; Beyond that, there isn&amp;rsquo;t much we can say.” - &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35205175&#34;&gt;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35205175&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given the rapid developments coming out of OpenAI, I think it’s unlikely that LLMs just end up being useful toys. There’s been a lot of goalposts shifting about what intelligence means. A few years ago it was the Turing test, now that GPT4 has &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/research/gpt-4&#34;&gt;blown away nearly every standardized test&lt;/a&gt;, I think it’s safe to say that white-collar work is at serious risk. As far as accidentally destroying humanity, that’s a toss up, but there isn’t a ton of evidence for that right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few of my predictions for what it means for white-collar work and the future of information management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Tips for Dealing With Vendors</title>
      <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/vendor_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosslazer.com/posts/vendor_management/</guid>
      <description>In my day-to-day role at Observe Inc., I work with a lot of vendors. I’ve been involved in all stages of vendor management, from procurement to rollout to renewal, for both software and contractors. The following is a list of tips I’ve found helpful when dealing with them. Whether they’re a SaaS provider, recruiter, web development shop, or more this advice is generally applicable.
Output is proportional to input This is a tip I got from our CEO during my first month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use It or Lose It: Implementing Usage-Based Pricing (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/use-it-or-lose-it-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosslazer.com/posts/use-it-or-lose-it-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://rosslazer.com/posts/use-it-or-lose-it-p1&#34;&gt;part 1&lt;/a&gt;, I talked about why you should implement a usage-based pricing model, now let’s get into the meat of how you actually implement one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use It or Lose It: Why Usage-Based Pricing (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/use-it-or-lose-it-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosslazer.com/posts/use-it-or-lose-it-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inspired much by the success of companies like Snowflake, &lt;a href=&#34;https://observeinc.com/&#34;&gt;Observe Inc.&lt;/a&gt; set out to build a usage based pricing model. I’ve learned a ton from this process and continue to do so each week. This blog series will catalog our journey and things I wish we had known on day 1. It’s broken up into 3 parts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why Usage Based Pricing?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How you implement it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Its challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Tooling</title>
      <link>https://rosslazer.com/posts/startup-tooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosslazer.com/posts/startup-tooling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/3oKIPqsXYcdjcBcXL2/giphy-downsized-large.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Tool gif&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the first product hire at &lt;a href=&#34;https://observeinc.com/&#34;&gt;Observe Inc.&lt;/a&gt;, I was tasked with bringing in a lot of tooling to solve problems. I’ve put together this list in the hopes of making the journey easier for others. Feel free to submit a PR if there’s more you think I should add.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
